const data = {
  quizes: {
    react: {
      "10 react questions": {
        questions: [
          {
            question: "What is a react component?",
            options: [
              "A blank blank ...",
              "The blank blank ...",
              "What a blank blank ...",
              "Blank the blank ...",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "0",
          },
          {
            question: "What is let?",
            options: [
              "A blank blank ...",
              "The blank blank ...",
              "What a blank blank ...",
              "Blank the blank ...",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "3",
          },
          {
            question: "What is const?",
            options: [
              "A blank blank ...",
              "The blank blank ...",
              "What a blank blank ...",
              "Blank the blank ...",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "2",
          },
          {
            question: "What is var?",
            options: [
              "A blank blank ...",
              "The blank blank ...",
              "What a blank blank ...",
              "Blank the blank ...",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "1",
          },
        ],
        saved: false,
      },
      "15 react questions": {
        questions: [
          {
            question: "What is var?",
            options: [
              "A blank blank ...",
              "The blank blank ...",
              "What a blank blank ...",
              "Blank the blank ...",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "0",
          },
          {
            question: "What is const",
            options: [
              "A blank blank ...",
              "The blank blank ...",
              "What a blank blank ...",
              "Blank the blank ...",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "2",
          },
        ],
        saved: false,
      },
      // "20 react questions": {},
      // "25 react questions": {},
      // "30 react questions": {},
      // "35 react questions": {},
      // "40 react questions": {},
      // "45 react questions": {},
      // "50 react questions": {},
      // "55 react questions": {},
      // "60 react questions": {},
      // "65 react questions": {},
      // "70 react questions": {},
      // "75 react questions": {},
      // "80 react questions": {},
      // "85 react questions": {},
      // "90 react questions": {},
      // "95 react questions": {},
      // "100 react questions": {},
    },
    nodejs: {
      "10 nodejs questions": {
        questions: [
          {
            question: "What is ...",
            options: [
              "A blank blank ...",
              "The blank blank ...",
              "What a blank blank ...",
              "Blank the blank ...",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "0",
          },
          {
            question: "What is ...",
            options: [
              "A blank blank ...",
              "The blank blank ...",
              "What a blank blank ...",
              "Blank the blank ...",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "3",
          },
        ],
        saved: false,
      },
      "15 nodejs questions": {
        questions: [
          {
            question: "What is ...",
            options: [
              "A blank blank ...",
              "The blank blank ...",
              "What a blank blank ...",
              "Blank the blank ...",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "0",
          },
          {
            question: "What is ...",
            options: [
              "A blank blank ...",
              "The blank blank ...",
              "What a blank blank ...",
              "Blank the blank ...",
            ],
            correctAnswer: "2",
          },
        ],
        saved: false,
      },
    },
    django: {
      "10 django questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
      "15 django questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
    },
    vue: {
      "10 vue questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
      "15 vue questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
    },
    angular: {
      "10 angular questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
      "15 angular questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
    },
    other: {
      "10 django questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
      "15 django questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
    },
    something: {
      "10 vue questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
      "15 vue questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
    },
    else: {
      "10 angular questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
      "15 angular questions": {
        questions: [],
        saved: false,
      },
    },
  },
};

export default data;
